onlinetroubleshooters.com 2019-01-14

# Privacy Policy Hosting - Security Policy - Online Trouble Shooters

  * __  011 3923 7777
  * __  091 888 2222 677

By submitting an online order form, or by using Online Trouble Shooters service, Customer hereby agrees to the following Privacy Policy. Customer agrees that it shall comply with and require its end users to comply with this Privacy Policy, Online Trouble Shooters Terms of Service (TOS), Online Trouble Shooters Acceptable Use Policy (AUP), and Online Trouble Shooters No-Spam Policy (NSP). In this document, the word “Agreement,” with a capital “A,” refers to the TOS, the AUP, the NSP, and the Privacy Policy collectively. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Online Trouble Shooters Privacy Officer by e-mail at info@onlinetroubleshooters.com.

## **1\. Introduction**

Online Trouble Shooters respects the privacy of every individual who visits its Web sites and uses its services. This privacy statement provides notice of the standards and terms under which Online Trouble Shooters protects the privacy of information supplied by visitors to sites on the World Wide Web that are owned and operated by Online Trouble Shooters including www.onlinetroubleshooters.com. This privacy statement provides notice of our information collection practices and of the ways in which your information may be used. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this information. 

## **2\. Personally Identifiable Information**

Online Trouble Shooters typically receives specific data about its Web site visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when our visitors request information, purchase or enroll for services, provide resume information for employment opportunities, or send us e-mail. Of course, some of these activities require that you give us information, such as when you make a purchase, use a credit card or electronic payment service to pay for Online Trouble Shooters services, submit your resume, or request certain types of information. 

## **We collect the following types of information about you.**

**Contact Information:**

1\. Name  
2\. Company  
3\. Postal Address  
4\. City  
6\. State  
7\. Country  
8\. Zip code or postal code  
9\. Email address  
10\. Telephone number  
11\. Fax number  
12\. Internet domain name

**Financial Information**

1\. Credit or debit card information  
2\. Cardholder name  
3\. Card number  
4\. Type of card (e.g, Visa, Mastercard)  
6\. Expiration date  
7\. Security code  
8\. Paypal account information  
9\. Email address of PayPal account

**Verification Data**

* Internet Protocol (IP) address for fraud-prevention purposes 

When you provide personally identifiable information to Online Trouble Shooters through one of our Web sites, it will be used to fulfill your specific request. However, Online Trouble Shooters reserves the right, in its discretion, to send you bulletins and other important information about your Online Trouble Shooters services. 

Online Trouble Shooters currently only sends service communication e-mails through www.onlinetroubleshooters.com, and does not send marketing e-mails or newsletters through www.onlinetroubleshooters.com. The service communication e-mails are essential to our registering you for service and to our continuing provision of services to you. Therefore, you may not opt out of receiving these e-mail messages. 

Online Trouble Shooters will not, however, sell, trade, or otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so, or in the case of imminent physical harm to any person. On those Online Trouble Shooters sites where you may provide Online Trouble Shooters with credit card, electronic payment service, or other ordering information via the Web, Online Trouble Shooters protects and secures this information by employing commercially customary Web-based security and encryption protocols, an example of which is the Secure Socket Layer (SSL). On those sites where you voluntarily offer any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like, Online Trouble Shooters will treat that portion of the information as non-confidential and non-proprietary and, except as otherwise expressed in this privacy statement, Online Trouble Shooters assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure. 

## **3\. Non-Personally Identifiable (Generic) Information**

In general, Online Trouble Shooters gathers some generic information automatically. Generic information does not reveal the identity of the visitor. It usually includes information about the Internet address assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors, and the Online Trouble Shooters sites visited. Online Trouble Shooters gathers this information for the limited purpose of determining customer service and Web site needs. We accomplish this by using certain technologies including “cookies” (a technology that can be used to provide the visitor with tailored information about Online Trouble Shooters services). Online Trouble Shooters does not combine information collected in this way with any personally identifiable information. You can set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse it. However, refusing some cookies may make it impossible to use or navigate the Online Trouble Shooters Web site properly. 

## **4\. Your OTs-Hosted Web Site, Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third Party Sites**

Information that you disclose in a public space including on any bulletin board, chat room, or Web site that Online Trouble Shooters may host for you as part of your Online Trouble Shooters services, is available to anyone else who visits that space. Online Trouble Shooters cannot safeguard any information you disclose in these locations. Additionally, Online Trouble Shooters Web sites may contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to OTs. Online Trouble Shooters cannot protect any information you may disclose at these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.

The Live Chat system that Online Trouble Shooters uses for customer support is a one-on-one chat. Online Trouble Shooters owns or licenses the Live Chat software and operates it on Online Trouble Shooters server and network. No third party collects any information that you provide through the Live Chat system. Online Trouble Shooters may retain and use logs of the Live Chat sessions for any of the following purposes: 

* to analyze and resolve system problems;  
* to compile and update frequently asked questions (FAQ) and entries in the customer support Knowledge Base;  
* to report problems to and obtain technical support from Online Trouble Shooters vendors, suppliers, or service providers;  
* to train personnel providing support to customers via Live Chat;  
* to evaluate the job performance of personnel providing support to customers via Live Chat;  
* to measure the effectiveness of Live Chat in providing support to customers;  
* to improve the quality and effectiveness of Live Chat in providing support to customers; or  
* to perform any other internal task related to providing services to Online Trouble Shooters customers, provided that performance of the task does not require disclosure of any of the contents of a chat session without the customer’s prior permission. 

## **5\. Exceptions and Limitations**

Not with standing the foregoing and in compliance with applicable laws, Online Trouble Shooters (i) cooperates fully with state, local, and any related officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to OTs) or purported unlawful activities of any user of the Online Trouble Shooters Service, and (ii) takes reasonable measures to protect its proprietary rights. For the limited purposes of accomplishing such cooperation and measures and in compliance with applicable laws, Online Trouble Shooters may be required to disclose personally identifiable information.

In addition, Online Trouble Shooters may elect to monitor the areas of communication of any kind (i) to satisfy any law, regulation, or government request;

(ii) if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate Online Trouble Shooters business; or (iii) to protect the rights or property of Online Trouble Shooters or others. 

## **6\. Sale or Transfer of Online Trouble Shooters Stock or Assets**

In connection with the potential or actual sale or transfer of any of its interest in www.onlinetroubleshooters.com, and other sites owned by Zone Networks, and any of the assets or stock of the company, Online Trouble Shooters reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including, but not limited to, name, address information, and other information you provided to Online Trouble Shooters) to a third party that (i) concentrates its business in Web hosting or communication products or services; (ii) agrees to be Online Trouble Shooters successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of information collected and maintained by Online Trouble Shooters; and (iii) agrees to the obligations of this privacy statement. To the extent it is practicable to do so, this paragraph shall also apply in the event of any bankruptcy proceedings involving Online Trouble Shooters. 

In the event that Online Trouble Shooters plans to transfer your information to a third party incident to a potential or actual sale of any of Online Trouble Shooters assets or stock, or incident to any bankruptcy proceedings involving Online Trouble Shooters, Online Trouble Shooters will: 

* Notify you by e-mail, at the e-mail address then on file for your account, at least thirty (30) days prior to the transfer taking place; and  
* Give you the opportunity to decide whether you wish for your information to be transferred to the third party. Please note, however, that if you choose not to allow your information to be transferred to the third party, you may have to terminate or cancel your service with Online Trouble Shooters At the time of providing notice to you of the upcoming transfer of information to a third party, Online Trouble Shooters will tell you whether you will have to terminate or cancel your service, should you decide not to allow Online Trouble Shooters to transfer your information to the third party. 

## **7\. Applicable Laws**

AS A MATERIAL CONDITION OF USING THIS WEB SITE OR Online Trouble Shooters HOSTING SERVICES, OR BOTH, CUSTOMER AND Online Trouble Shooters AGREE THAT THE USE OF THIS SITE IS BOUND AND GOVERNED BY THE LAWS OF THE STATE OF INDIA, REGARDLESS OF WHERE CUSTOMER MAY RESIDE, ACCESS THE INTERNET, OR CONDUCT HIS, HER, OR ITS BUSINESS.

MOREOVER, CUSTOMER ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES THAT Online Trouble Shooter RECEIVES AND STORES PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ON SERVERS LOCATED WITHIN THE INDIA FURTHERMORE, CUSTOMER ACKNOWLEDGES AND AGREES TO SUCH FLOWS OF HIS OR HER PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ACROSS BORDERS FROM HIS OR HER COUNTRY TO INDIA. 

## **8\. Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes in this privacy statement, on the home page, and in other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

## **9\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: info@onlinetroubleshooters.com. 

## **10\. Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by making the change on our member information page or by e-mailing our Customer Support at info@onlinetroubleshooters.com. 

## **11\. Sharing of Information**

**Agents**   
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any purposes other than to bill you for our services. 

**Service Providers**   
We use other third parties to provide various additional services for you on our Web site. When you sign up for the additional services, we will share certain elements of the information you provide to us as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

**Data Backup Policy**   
Online Trouble Shooters doesn’t guarantee any kind of data backup service till it is classified, it is the responsibility of any loss of data of website or email, the same is not the responsibility of Online Trouble Shooters. All customers needs to take there backups on intervals to avoid any uncertain failures. 

## Need to ask? Create Ticket or Call Our Team 24x7 

  *
